I went to Yumo painting and calligraphy shop
유모 그림과 서예 가게에 다녀왔어요
to convey information to him.
그에게 정보를 전달하기 위해.
Work with him.
그와 함께 일하세요.
And today,
그리고 오늘,
we are both in cahoots
우리 둘 다 협력 중이야
identified the two drug dealers.
두 명의 마약상을 확인했습니다.
The purpose is
목적은
to give it time
시간을 주기 위해
pkt at the tea shop.
찻집에서 pkt.
And also
그리고 또한
You mean I'm Plum Blossom Four?
내가 매화 4호라는 뜻인가요?
I am "Plum Blossom Si".
저는 "매화씨" 입니다.
Komandan Luo.
코만단 루오.
Check it carefully.
주의 깊게 확인하십시오.
If you don't check, you're an asshole.
확인하지 않으면 당신은 바보입니다.
Really anxious.
정말 불안해요.
sister,
자매,
you're not much better than Zhao An,
당신은 Zhao An보다 훨씬 낫지 않습니다.
your mind is narrow.
당신의 마음은 좁습니다.
Manager Luo,
루오 매니저님,
what about this old road?
이 오래된 길은 어때요?
Keep hanging.
계속 매달리세요.
Hang him until he dies.
죽을 때까지 매달아 두세요.
Section Chief Chen
첸 과장
gun barge
총 바지선
own weight is around 1,100 grams,
자신의 몸무게는 약 1,100그램이고,
after pouring it weighs approximately 1350 grams
부은 후 무게는 약 1350g입니다.
the weight of that gun
그 총의 무게
about 1,200 grams.
약 1,200그램.
Not a full weapon
완전한 무기는 아니다
nor is it an empty weapon
빈 무기도 아니지
there is one possibility
가능성이 하나 있어
already fired several bullets,
이미 총알 여러 발을 발사했고,
but it looks like the gun has a problem
그런데 총에 문제가 있는 것 같아
So
그래서
is not firing a few bullets
총알 몇 발 안 쏴
but the magazine contains empty bullets.
하지만 탄창에는 빈 총알이 들어있습니다.
You still have to figure out how to get to the bookstore.
당신은 여전히 ​​서점에 가는 방법을 알아내야 합니다.
Good.
좋은.
Room upstairs.
위층에 있는 방.
In the middle of the floor, seventh floor.
7층 중앙, 7층.
I saved some papers and documents.
나는 몇 가지 서류와 문서를 저장했습니다.
You choose what is worthless.
당신은 쓸모없는 것을 선택합니다.
Give it to Luo Guanqun.
Luo Guanqun에게주세요.
The rest must be thrown away.
나머지는 버려야 합니다.
Good.
좋은.
Second floor balcony.
2층 발코니.
I put a pot of yellow chrysanthemums,
노란 국화 화분을 꽂았는데,
is a safe signal.
안전한 신호입니다.
You changed Huang Ju to Zi Ju,
Huang Ju를 Zi Ju로 바꾸셨고,
indicates something has happened.
어떤 일이 일어났음을 나타냅니다.
And most importantly
그리고 가장 중요한 것은
4th brother plum blossom.
넷째오빠 매화.
Be sure to investigate Shan's plans
Shan의 계획을 꼭 조사하세요.
have to destroy it.
그것을 파괴해야합니다.
Of course.
물론.
Enough already.
이미 충분합니다.
I've ordered
주문했어요
everyone will die.
모두가 죽을 것이다.
Die according to the desired state
원하는 상태에 따라 죽는다
deserve it
그럴만 한 자격이
i...
나...
I'll think of a way
방법을 생각해 볼게요
think of ways to please you.
당신을 기쁘게 할 방법을 생각해 보세요.
No need.
필요 없음.
I can hold it.
나는 그것을 잡을 수 있습니다.
I hear
나는 듣는다
when people almost die
사람들이 거의 죽을 때
can see the person he most wants to see.
가장 보고 싶은 사람을 볼 수 있다.
You can see the person you most want to see.
가장 보고 싶은 사람을 볼 수 있습니다.
If it's really like that,
정말 그런 상황이라면,
I'm not afraid of how long the death process will be.
나는 죽음의 과정이 얼마나 오래 걸릴지 두렵지 않습니다.
Because there are those who accompany me.
동행하는 이들이 있기 때문이다.
The old way
옛날 방식
no matter where you end up.
당신이 어디에서 끝나든 상관없습니다.
We will fight together
우리는 함께 싸울 것이다
fight together
함께 싸우다
Here
여기
addicted man
중독된 남자
Their sugar porridge and fried dumplings are the best.
설탕죽과 만두튀김이 최고예요.
Hurry up and try it.
서둘러서 시도해 보세요.
Me
나
I'm a little hungry.
조금 배가 고파요.
You two eat.
둘이서 먹어요
How
어떻게
used to be every night after overtime
초과근무 후에 매일 밤 그랬었지
I will come with my sister.
나는 여동생과 함께 올 것이다.
You still have a younger sibling.
아직 동생이 있어요.
But he died before living for 18 years.
하지만 그는 18년을 살기도 전에 세상을 떠났습니다.
How did he die?
그가 어떻게 죽었나요?
One night two years ago.
2년 전 어느 날 밤.
He came to take me home.
그는 나를 집에 데려가려고 왔습니다.
I met a group of drunk Japanese soldiers,
술취한 일본군을 만났는데,
then teased me.
그러다 나를 놀렸다.
Eat my tofu.
내 두부를 먹어라.
My sister is young.
내 여동생은 어리다.
Very angry,
매우 화가 났고,
even looking for them to debate.
심지어 토론할 사람들을 찾기도 합니다.
They use punctures
그들은 구멍을 사용합니다
stabbed him in the stomach.
그의 배를 찔렀습니다.
Case case
케이스 케이스
selling sugar porridge.
설탕죽을 팔아요.
3 kilograms jug, 4 kilograms shellfish.
주전자 3kg, 조개 4kg.
My little brother when he was little
내 남동생이 어렸을 때
I like reading this song the most.
나는 이 노래를 가장 읽는 것을 좋아한다.
You must hate Japanese people, right?
일본 사람을 싫어해야겠죠?
What's the point of hating?
미워하는 이유가 무엇입니까?
Can I beat them?
내가 그들을 이길 수 있을까?
If one day you go to war,
어느 날 전쟁에 나가게 된다면,
are you willing to give your life for your sister?
언니를 위해 목숨을 바칠 각오가 있나요?
Kak Hong Ling.
카홍링.
Why are we walking this path?
우리는 왜 이 길을 걷고 있는 걸까요?
Very dark.
매우 어두운.
This road is close.
이 도로는 가깝습니다.
Come in.
올.
In front of my house.
내 집 앞.
What dance are we learning today?
오늘은 어떤 춤을 배울까요?
Today I will teach you
오늘은 내가 가르쳐줄게
The most popular Foxtrot dance in Shanghai, how about it?
상하이에서 가장 인기 있는 폭스트롯 댄스, 어떠세요?
Tarian Foxtrot.
타리안 폭스트롯.
Previously I had read a novel
예전에 소설을 읽었었는데
Foxtrot dance called Shanghai.
상하이라는 폭스트롯 댄스.
The story is about a quiet little street.
이야기는 조용한 작은 거리에 관한 것입니다.
On a secluded little road.
한적한 작은 길에서.
It's terrible
끔찍하다
where there are so many murder cases
살인 사건이 너무 많은 곳
but on this road there are often rats
그런데 이 길에는 쥐가 자주 돌아요
addicted man
중독된 남자
I'm most afraid of mice.
나는 쥐를 가장 무서워한다.
Can you walk in front of me?
내 앞으로 걸어갈 수 있나요?
Then you follow me.
그럼 당신은 나를 따르십시오.
Red.
빨간색.
Big Brother Hong Ling.
홍링 형님.
You...
너...
Why do you do like this?
왜 이런 짓을 하는 걸까요?
Didn't think of it, right?
생각지도 못했어요, 그렇죠?
I put medicine in your sugar porridge.
나는 당신의 설탕 죽에 약을 넣었습니다.
How
어떻게
kill him.
그를 죽여.
How to do it?
어떻게 하나요?
Like you said
네가 말했듯이
pass through the small road
작은 길을 지나
shot him twice in the back.
뒤에서 그를 두 번 쐈습니다.
You didn't lie to me?
나한테 거짓말한 거 아니었어?
You should have heard the sound of the gun, right?
총소리를 들었어야 했죠?
But I heard gunshots a long time ago.
그런데 오래 전에 총소리가 들렸어요.
Why are you only coming back now?
왜 이제서야 돌아오시나요?
Taking care of the corpse
시체를 돌보는 중
doesn't need time?
시간은 필요하지 않아?
Good.
좋은.
Good work.
잘 했어.
Have you taken medicine?
약을 먹었나요?
Already.
이미.
Has the bandage been changed?
붕대가 바뀌었나요?
Not yet.
아직 아님.
I'll help you.
내가 도와 줄게.
Good.
좋은.
Hong Ling.
홍 링.
Shi Yang was entrusted by the Chongqing military
시양은 충칭군으로부터 위임을 받았다
had to lurk for a long time.
오랫동안 숨어 지내야 했다.
He got important information
그는 중요한 정보를 얻었습니다
but he didn't submit
하지만 그 사람은 제출하지 않았어
he ran away.
그는 도망 갔다.
He threatened the headquarters to ransom the information for big money.
그는 큰 돈을 받고 정보를 몸값으로 요구하겠다고 본사를 위협했습니다.
What information did he get?
그는 어떤 정보를 얻었나요?
Japanese Army Ministry's plan to counterfeit French money.
일본 육군성의 프랑스 화폐 위조 계획.
If you lose this information,
해당 정보를 분실한 경우,
Counterfeit French money will spread in this country
프랑스 위조지폐가 이 나라에 퍼질 것입니다
the financial system will collapse
금융시스템이 붕괴될 것이다
war stuff gets worse
전쟁 상황이 악화됨
our victory is getting farther away.
우리의 승리는 점점 멀어지고 있습니다.
This is the price you deserve
이게 당신이 받을 만한 가격이에요
for your bright future.
당신의 밝은 미래를 위해.
I just don't want to kill innocent people.
나는 단지 무고한 사람들을 죽이고 싶지 않을 뿐입니다.
About what he did
그 사람이 한 일에 대해서
I don't care
난 상관없어
I don't care.
나는 상관하지 않는다.
Do you care?
당신은 관심이 있습니까?
You and Shi Yang are not the same person,
당신과 Shi Yang은 같은 사람이 아닙니다.
conscience?
양심?
Justice
정당성
in your heart, nothing is destroyed.
당신의 마음에는 아무것도 파괴되지 않습니다.
You will definitely help me
넌 분명 나에게 도움이 될 거야
why steal my pendant
왜 내 펜던트를 훔쳐?
I was wrong
내가 틀렸어
I asked why you stole my locket
왜 내 로켓을 훔쳤냐고 물었더니
that woman lied to me
그 여자가 나한테 거짓말을 했어
you didn't kill him.
당신은 그를 죽이지 않았습니다.
Why don't you kill him?
그를 죽이는 게 어때?
The woman told me
그 여자가 나한테 말했어
if I give you your pendant
내가 네 펜던트를 주면
will share half the money you receive
당신이 받는 돈의 절반을 공유할 것입니다
I was wrong, I was really wrong.
내가 틀렸어, 내가 정말 틀렸어.
Rotten bitch.
썩은년아.
I I
II
turned out to trap me behind.
나를 뒤에 가두는 것으로 밝혀졌습니다.
I am wrong.
나는 틀렸다.
I have gambling debts,
도박 빚이 있는데,
I can't pay.
지불할 수 없습니다.
They can kill me.
그들은 나를 죽일 수 있습니다.
I beg you.
부탁드립니다.
I beg you, I was wrong
부탁이야, 내가 틀렸어
don't kill me.
나를 죽이지 마십시오.
where is he
그 사람은 어디 있어?
Old factory.
오래된 공장.
Is it in the old factory?
오래된 공장에 있나요?
Take me to find him.
나를 데리고 그를 찾아보세요.
I will take you away.
나는 당신을 데려 갈 것입니다.
I took you to find him.
그를 찾으려고 당신을 데려갔죠.
He is waiting for me.
그는 나를 기다리고 있습니다.
You can kill him,
당신은 그를 죽일 수 있습니다,
if you dare play tricks again,
감히 다시 장난을 친다면,
I will shoot you dead.
나는 당신을 쏘아 죽일 것입니다.
He's in the old factory in front of it
그 사람은 그 앞에 있는 오래된 공장에 있어요
wait for me on the second floor.
2층에서 기다려 주세요.
do not forget
잊지 마요
The muzzle of my gun is behind you
내 총구는 네 뒤에 있어
understand?
이해하다?
He is very alert,
그는 매우 경계심이 많고,
I'll go calm him down first.
내가 먼저 그를 진정시키러 갈게.
Don't mess around.
엉망으로 만들지 마십시오.
Xiao Tao.
샤오 타오.
I've been found out!
나는 알아냈다!
Shi Yang is now outside.
시양은 지금 밖에 있어요.
Inside the pendant there is no information.
펜던트 안에는 정보가 없습니다.
He lied to me
그는 나에게 거짓말을 했어요
I came to tell you
나는 당신에게 말하러 왔습니다
there are still other clues that can find it.
그것을 찾을 수 있는 다른 단서가 아직 남아 있습니다.
Shi Yang has heart disease?
시양에게 심장병이 있나요?
Every Thursday
매주 목요일
going to Ci'an hospital to look for a doctor
의사를 찾으러 시안 병원에 가다
to take a drug called nitroglycerin.
니트로글리세린이라는 약을 복용합니다.
Ci'an Hospital.
시안병원.
You go quickly.
빨리 가세요.
Hurry up.
서둘러요.
So what about you?
그래서 당신은 어때요?
Do not mind me.
신경쓰지 마세요.
I think it's for my sister's sake.
아무래도 언니를 위해서인 것 같아요.
But I can't leave you.
하지만 나는 당신을 떠날 수 없습니다.
Don't worry, he won't do anything to me
걱정하지 마세요. 그 사람은 나한테 아무 짓도 안 할 거예요.
you go quickly, you go quickly!
빨리 가세요 빨리 가세요!
Bitch woman!
개년아!
Betray me!
나를 배신해라!
Go away!
저리 가요!
Die!
주사위!
If one day you go to war,
어느 날 전쟁에 나가게 된다면,
would you be willing to give your life for your sister?
당신은 당신의 여동생을 위해 당신의 생명을 기꺼이 바칠 수 있습니까?
Dad is home.
아빠가 집에 있어요.
My son.
내 아들.
Ayah.
유모.
Obedient or not?
순종하는가 아닌가?
Good son.
좋은 아들.
Ayah.
유모.
Why did you come home so late?
왜 이렇게 늦게 집에 왔나요?
Dad has a lot to do
아빠는 할 일이 많아요
So why haven't you slept yet?
그럼 왜 아직 잠을 자지 않았나요?
He says
그는 말한다
have to wait for you to come back to tell the tale
당신이 이야기를 하기 위해 돌아올 때까지 기다려야 해요
he just slept
그는 방금 잤어
Good.
좋은.
Dad will tell you a story.
아빠가 이야기를 들려줄 거예요.
What do you want to hear?
무엇을 듣고 싶나요?
About tin soldiers?
주석 병사에 대해서요?
That...
저것...
Persistent soldier.
끈질긴 군인.
Those little soldiers, right?
그 작은 군인들 맞죠?
Correct.
옳은.
Dad will tell you.
아빠가 말씀하실 거예요.
Once upon a time,
옛날 옛적에,
there was a soldier
군인이 있었어요
he always carried a gun on his shoulder.
그는 항상 어깨에 총을 메고 다녔다.
Bold and cool.
대담하고 멋지다.
Dad, someday I will also hold a gun.
아빠, 나도 언젠가는 총을 쥐게 될 거예요.
Good.
좋은.
Our future fans
우리 미래의 팬
also carries a Maoser pistol on his shoulder.
또한 그의 어깨에는 Maoser 권총을 들고 있습니다.
Bold and cool.
대담하고 멋지다.
On the table.
책상 위에.
There are lots of other toys.
다른 장난감도 많아요.
There is a beautiful paper dancer
아름다운 종이 댄서가 있어요
he wears a
그는 입는다
a beautiful rose brooch.
아름다운 장미 브로치.
This little soldier really likes it.
이 작은 군인은 그것을 정말 좋아합니다.
Every day looking at him,
매일 그 사람을 바라보며,
dream one day
어느 날 꿈을 꾸다
to be his bride.
그의 신부가 되려고.
However, there is a little monster.
그런데 작은 괴물이 있어요.
Deeply hates Xiao Xi's army.
Xiao Xi의 군대를 매우 싫어합니다.
As long as he's not focused
그 사람이 집중하지 않는 이상
threw it into the furnace
그것을 용광로에 던졌다
is Xiao Xi Bing sick?
샤오시빙 아픈가요?
Of course it hurts.
물론 아프다.
But Xiao Xi's soldiers were very brave.
그러나 Xiao Xi의 병사들은 매우 용감했습니다.
Even though the flames had engulfed his body,
불길이 그의 몸을 삼켰음에도 불구하고,
and melted his body slowly,
그리고 천천히 몸을 녹였다.
however, he remained strong.
그러나 그는 여전히 강했다.
With force.
힘으로.
At this time,
이때,
suddenly there was a strong wind.
갑자기 강한 바람이 불었습니다.
through the wind,
바람을 통해,
the beautiful dancer flies.
아름다운 댄서가 날아간다.
Fly, fly
날아라, 날아라
terbang ke samping Xiao Xijin.
terbang ke samping Xiao Xijin.
Sister!
자매!
Sis.
언니.
Look at it.
보세요.
Lu seemed to be saying something.
루가 뭔가 말하고 있는 것 같았다.
Come on, listen.
자, 들어보세요.
Harder.
더 세게.
Abandoned by the dancer.
댄서에게 버림받았습니다.
Rose brooch.
장미 브로치.
What's that?
그게 뭐야?
What rose brooch?
무슨 장미 브로치요?
Maybe it's important information.
어쩌면 중요한 정보일지도 모르겠습니다.
Finally he confessed.
마침내 그는 고백했다.
Listen again.
다시 들어보세요.
From now on
지금부터
them
그들을
will be together forever.
영원히 함께 할 것입니다.
What's together again?
또 무슨 일이야?
Which other communist members were you with?
다른 공산주의자들 중 누구와 함께 있었나요?
Say.
말하다.
What is your online account?
귀하의 온라인 계정은 무엇입니까?
Say it.
말해.
Is dead.
죽었어.
Just opened your mouth
방금 입을 열었다
didn't say anything already died.
이미 죽었다는 말은 안 했어.
Go away
저리 가요
everyone will die.
모두가 죽을 것이다.
Die according to the desired state
원하는 상태에 따라 죽는다
That's appropriate.
적절합니다.
Keep your hands away.
손을 멀리하십시오.
Leopard sellers eat together
표범 판매자가 함께 식사합니다
hold on, hold on
잠깐만, 잠깐만
keep your hands away
손을 멀리하세요
everyone stand still, don't move!
다들 가만히 있어요, 움직이지 마세요!
Grand Princess.
그랜드 프린세스.
Look at that person,
저 사람 좀 봐,
look familiar?
낯익어 보여?
You look it
당신은 그것을 본다
a little nervous.
조금 긴장.
Look at it.
보세요.
The money is gone.
돈이 없어졌습니다.
Going home I couldn't explain to my wife and children.
집에 돌아와서 아내와 아이들에게 설명할 수 없었습니다.
Like...
좋다...
Where have you met?
어디서 만났나요?
I've remembered.
나는 기억했다.
That day at the Divine Hai Sect's Tea House,
그날 신해종의 찻집에서
he was one of the tea guests in the private room on the second floor.
그는 2층 개인실의 차 손님 중 한 명이었다.
Correct.
옳은.
However, at that time I did not suspect them.
그러나 그 당시 나는 그들을 의심하지 않았습니다.
Then let it all go.
그런 다음 모두 놓아 두십시오.
The person the military police are looking for is definitely him.
헌병대가 찾고 있는 사람은 틀림없이 그 사람이다.
If not,
그렇지 않다면,
shall we report him?
그 사람을 신고할까?
You can still make a contribution.
여전히 기여할 수 있습니다.
Pig brains.
돼지 두뇌.
If this person is taken away by the military police,
만약 이 사람이 헌병에게 연행된다면,
are we still doing great?
우리 아직도 잘 지내?
So how?
그래서 방법?
Tuan Zhang
투안 장
lucky today too.
오늘도 운이 좋다.
Fortunately.
다행스럽게도.
You still say you can't play.
아직도 놀 수 없다고 하더군요.
Next time together
다음에는 함께해요
Ping family
핑 가족
I can't sleep.
잠이 안 와요.
Can't you sleep either?
너도 잠 못 자?
Can you dance?
당신은 춤을 수 있습니다?
It's like we never danced.
우리는 춤을 춰본 적이 없는 것 같아요.
According to you,
당신에 따르면,
what is moonlight?
달빛이 뭐야?
Untouched.
손대지 않은.
Also untouched.
또한 손길이 닿지 않았습니다.
So...
그래서...
His presence
그의 존재
like a lot of big things
많은 큰 일을 좋아한다
the eternal.
영원한.
Even though he disappeared,
그 사람이 사라졌는데도,
but he was still there.
하지만 그는 아직 거기에 있었어요.
I can feel
나는 느낄 수있다
today you are very sad.
오늘 당신은 매우 슬프다.
Is it true?
사실인가요?
It means
그 뜻은
you're sad too.
당신도 슬퍼요.
Today we don't fight anymore.
오늘 우리는 더 이상 싸우지 않습니다.
Accompany me like this, how about it?
이렇게 동행해 주시는 건 어떨까요?
Okay
좋아요
section chief Chen
첸 과장
Did you go to work early today?
오늘 일찍 출근하셨나요?
Where's the newspaper?
신문은 어디에 있나요?
Has it arrived?
도착했나요?
It's arrived, it's done.
도착했어요, 끝났어요.
Here.
여기.
Your new declaration and newspaper.
귀하의 새로운 선언문과 신문.
Good.
좋은.
Thank You.
감사합니다.
No need to hesitate.
주저할 필요가 없습니다.
The act of printing fake money is called Project Shan.
가짜 돈을 인쇄하는 행위를 프로젝트 샨(Project Shan)이라고 합니다.
Hear - hear other than money
듣다 - 돈 이외의 것을 듣다
the Japanese are still trying to fake it
일본인들은 아직도 그것을 속이려고 노력하고 있습니다.
coins issued in parts of the CCP border
중국 공산당 국경 지역에서 발행된 동전
there are two military spies hiding in Yan'an
옌안에는 두 명의 군 간첩이 숨어 있습니다
took away copper coins,
구리 동전을 빼앗아갔습니다.
and printing paper
그리고 인쇄용지
xi Que is the general of the army.
Xi Que는 군대의 장군입니다.
Liuli Guoguo often went to the dance hall these two days.
Liuli Guoguo는 이틀 동안 댄스홀에 자주갔습니다.
What is related to this problem?
이 문제와 관련된 것은 무엇입니까?
Didn't ask me recently if it happened
최근에 그런 일이 있었는지 묻지 않았어
cases related to dance halls
댄스홀 관련 사건
I actually remember it
사실 기억나는데
two days ago there was a murder case.
이틀 전에 살인 사건이 있었습니다.
The deceased was a female dancer.
사망자는 여성 댄서였다.
Where did the incident occur?
사건은 어디서 발생했나요?
In an abandoned factory
버려진 공장에서
the victim was named Cai Hongling
피해자의 이름은 Cai Hongling이었습니다.
female dancers in the Xianle ballroom
Xianle 연회장의 여성 무용수들
the cause of death was
사망 원인은
shot.
발사.
Shot three times
세 번 쐈어
and fell from the 2nd floor
그리고 2층에서 떨어졌어요
Immediately died on the spot.
그 자리에서 즉시 사망했다.
This man.
이 사람.
Has this man been found?
이 사람이 발견됐나요?
Not yet.
아직 아님.
He had indeed seen it
그 사람은 실제로 그것을 본 적이 있었어
traces of a man's life in his house.
집에 남아 있는 남자의 삶의 흔적.
But after asking people around,
그런데 주변 사람들에게 물어보니
they all said that he didn't know what this man was
다들 그 사람이 어떤 사람인지 모른다고 하더군요
is it true that this man lives in his house?
이 사람이 자기 집에 산다는 게 사실인가요?
No wonder Guoguo wanted to go to the dance hall these two days.
Guoguo가 이틀 동안 댄스홀에 가고 싶어한 것도 당연합니다.
It turns out he wanted to approach Xi Que through Cai Hongling.
그는 Cai Hongling을 통해 Xi Que에게 접근하고 싶었던 것으로 밝혀졌습니다.
But why do you want to look?
그런데 왜 보고 싶은 걸까요?
their own people?
자기 사람들?
Why so much interest in this case?
이 사건에 왜 그렇게 관심이 많습니까?
I suspect,
예상 컨데,
This case is related to my wife.
이 사건은 내 아내와 관련된 사건이다.
Your wife.
당신의 아내.
Having a relationship with a female dancer?
여성 댄서와 관계를 맺고 있나요?
The last few nights were so sad,
지난 며칠 밤은 너무 슬펐어요
what Cai Hongling was killed
Cai Hongling이 살해당한 것
Cai Hongling to help him?
Cai Hongling이 그를 도와줄까요?
Maybe Liuli Guoguo knows the whereabouts of magpie.
아마도 Liuli Guoguo는 까치의 행방을 알고 있을지도 모릅니다.
That way you can get through
그래야 합격할 수 있다
to find it.
그것을 찾기 위해.
Why frown?
왜 눈살을 찌푸리나요?
What's wrong with your wife?
아내에게 무슨 문제가 있나요?
Maybe he has changed his mind?
어쩌면 그 사람 마음이 바뀌었나요?
I shouldn't have given away the green sofa that time.
그땐 녹색 소파를 내어주지 말았어야 했는데.
Go back to your car.
차로 돌아가세요.
Getting married is not easy.
결혼하는 것은 쉽지 않습니다.
Go!
가다!
Staying single is better.
싱글로 지내는 것이 더 좋습니다.
Second floor balcony.
2층 발코니.
I put a pot of yellow chrysanthemums,
노란 국화 화분을 꽂았는데,
is a safe signal.
안전한 신호입니다.
You changed Huang Ju to Zi Ju,
Huang Ju를 Zi Ju로 바꾸셨고,
indicates something has happened.
어떤 일이 일어났음을 나타냅니다.
I've obviously changed Huang Ju to Zi Ju.
분명히 Huang Ju를 Zi Ju로 변경했습니다.
Who put Huang Ju back?
누가 황주를 다시 데려왔는가?
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
I...
나...
Come buy things.
와서 물건을 사세요.
Purchase of goods?
상품구매?
This shop is closed.
이 가게는 문을 닫았습니다.
Isn't it still open?
아직 열려 있지 않나요?
Wait a minute
잠깐 기다려요
the boss of this restaurant, Boss Lu.
이 식당의 사장인 루보스.
He is a member of the CCP
그는 중국 공산당의 일원이다
has been arrested.
체포되었습니다.
Understand?
이해하다?
Is there anyone?
거기 아무도 없나요?
There are definitely people who want to impersonate old people
노인 흉내를 내고 싶은 사람도 분명 있을 것이다
ambush here.
여기서 매복하세요.
We still don't know the comrades who died on the old road.
우리는 아직도 옛 길에서 죽은 동지들을 모릅니다.
But how could this person know
그런데 이 사람이 어떻게 알겠어요?
security connection secret code?
보안 연결 비밀번호는요?
Are you a new doctor?
당신은 새로운 의사입니까?
Your lipstick color is very nice.
립스틱 색깔이 참 예쁘네요.
Buy where?
어디서 구매하세요?
When there is a discount at Yong'an Mall.
용안몰 할인이 있을 때.
I feel like the colors are too flashy.
색상이 너무 화려한 것 같아요.
How could it be
어떻게 그럴수있어
very suitable for your skin color
당신의 피부색에 매우 적합합니다
Is that true?
그게 사실인가요?
Correct
옳은
The aspirin you want is in locker number five
네가 원하는 아스피린은 5번 사물함에 있어
Thank You
감사합니다
get you a medicine bag.
약봉지 주세요.
Thank You.
감사합니다.
Take it.
가져.
Just sign here.
여기에 서명하시면 됩니다.
I also want to buy lipstick.
나도 립스틱 사고 싶다.
Two days later, we went to the mall together.
이틀 후, 우리는 함께 쇼핑몰에 갔습니다.
Good.
좋은.
You have really good taste.
정말 맛이 좋군요.
Later, help me with suggestions.
나중에 제안을 도와주세요.
You are so Beautiful
너무 아름다워요
whatever you wear, it's still beautiful.
무엇을 입든 여전히 아름답습니다.
Signed.
서명됨.
Good.
좋은.
Until found.
발견될 때까지.
Miss, wait a moment.
아가씨, 잠깐만요.
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
Nona,
노나,
your scarf fell.
네 스카프가 떨어졌어.
Thank You.
감사합니다.
Is there any clue about the magpie at Ci'an Hospital?
시안병원 까치에 대한 단서가 있나요?
Who is that doctor?
그 의사는 누구입니까?
Road.
도로.
Ping Family
핑 제품군
luFang
루팡
Long time no see
오랜만이에요
I've been transferred
나는 이전되었습니다
to the document room of the planning section of the military police headquarters.
헌병본부 기획과 문서실로.
It's been very busy lately.
최근에는 매우 바빴습니다.
Can't let go.
놓을 수 없습니다.
That is an important department.
그것은 중요한 부서입니다.
What important position?
어떤 중요한 직책인가요?
Out of the blue...
뜻밖에...
Because I can speak a little Japanese,
일본어를 조금 할 수 있기 때문에
making me have to run on both sides of the Gendarmerie Commander and Shangxing.
헌병대 사령관과 상싱의 양쪽에서 달려야하게 만들었습니다.
Very tiring.
매우 피곤합니다.
How about you?
당신은 어떤가요?
Came here to work.
일하러 여기에 왔습니다.
Do you know these people
이 사람들을 아시나요?
is what person?
어떤 사람이에요?
Member of the Chinese Communist Party.
중국공산당원.
these two days,
이 이틀,
military police have arrested many people,
헌병대가 많은 사람들을 체포했고,
So,
그래서,
how long are they detained?
얼마나 오랫동안 구금되어 있나요?
I heard he's going to be sent to detention,
그 사람이 감옥에 보내질 거라고 들었는데,
probably won't come back.
아마 돌아 오지 않을 것입니다.
Very scary.
매우 무섭습니다.
That...
저것...
Working for the Japanese,
일본인을 위해 일하고,
have to be more careful.
더 조심해야 합니다.
You too.
너도.
Then I'll go in first.
그럼 나 먼저 들어갈게.
Sir, is it finished?
선생님, 끝났어요?
Thank You.
감사합니다.
Okay.
좋아요.
You work first.
당신이 먼저 일하세요.
Back to chatting.
채팅으로 돌아갑니다.
Until found.
발견될 때까지.
Luo Guanqun had already grasped the old path.
Luo Guanqun은 이미 옛 길을 파악했습니다.
You've captured Jin Ming.
진밍을 사로잡았습니다.
You've been very accomplished lately.
당신은 최근에 매우 성취했습니다.
Lu, it was Luo Guan Qun who snatched my services.
Lu, 내 서비스를 빼앗은 사람은 Luo Guan Qun이었습니다.
He... He's outrageous.
그... 그 사람은 터무니없어요.
Luo Guan Qun has the ability.
Luo Guan Qun에는 능력이 있습니다.
You have your abilities.
당신은 당신의 능력을 가지고 있습니다.
My greatest ability
나의 가장 큰 능력
is loyal to Village Chief Mu.
마을 추장 무에게 충성합니다.
Your greatest ability
당신의 가장 큰 능력
is telling you to feed the horse
말에게 먹이를 주라고 하네요
or feeding pigs,
아니면 돼지에게 먹이를 주거나
you can even close
닫아도 돼
very strictly.
아주 엄격하게.
Luo Guanqun couldn't even put a finger in.
Luo Guanqun은 손가락 하나도 넣을 수 없었습니다.
I'm guarding your house.
나는 당신의 집을 지키고 있습니다.
Shan's project goes smoothly.
Shan의 프로젝트는 순조롭게 진행됩니다.
Now the scale is getting bigger.
이제 그 규모가 점점 커지고 있습니다.
Now the problem is,
이제 문제는,
lack of money.
돈이 부족합니다.
Your previous fundraising plans,
이전 모금 계획,
even though it is not used
비록 사용되지는 않지만
but I'm always optimistic.
하지만 저는 항상 낙관적이에요.
Mu Village Chief,
무마을 이장,
I promise,
약속해요
as long as it goes according to my plan,
내 계획대로 진행된다면,
will definitely give Shan project
확실히 Shan 프로젝트를 제공할 것입니다
money that Shan Jihua would never use up.
Shan Jihua가 결코 사용하지 않을 돈.
Trust me.
날 믿어.
Here.
여기.
Mu Village Chief,
무마을 이장,
I recently understood a logic.
나는 최근에 논리를 이해했습니다.
What principle?
어떤 원리?
It's actually this guy
사실 이 사람이에요
and horses are the same thing.
말도 마찬가지다.
What a good horse.
정말 좋은 말입니다.
Her skin can be seen from afar,
멀리서도 피부가 눈에 띄고,
take a closer look at the feet and hands
발과 손을 자세히 살펴보세요
front view wide chest,
정면도 넓은 가슴,
the back looks like a butt.
뒷모습이 엉덩이같네요.
Look at it.
보세요.
Do I look like Shinixuan Takeda?
내가 다케다 신수안처럼 보이나요?
Good.
좋은.
You...
너...
Truly a genius
진짜 천재야
Pagi, Qian Xiu Cai
파기, 첸 슈 카이
morning section chief Chen
아침과장 첸
where is the newspaper?
신문은 어디에 있나요?
Have arrived.
도착했습니다.
Your new declaration and newspaper.
귀하의 새로운 선언문과 신문.
Good.
좋은.
Section Chief Chen
첸 과장
I remember you first
나는 당신을 먼저 기억합니다
don't like seeing new announcements,
새로운 공지를 보는 것을 좋아하지 않습니다.
I also often forget it at my place.
나 역시 집에서는 종종 잊어버린다.
This is because in this latest announcement
그 이유는 이번 발표에서
created the Wang Du Lu martial arts novel series
왕두로 무협소설 시리즈 창작
kun Lun who was surprised
놀란 쿤룬
I feel addicted.
중독된 것 같아요.
Then, next time I'd like to see it too.
그럼 다음에는 저도 꼭 보고 싶습니다.
Don't you look at your Eastern Zhou country records anymore?
더 이상 저우동부 국가 기록을 보지 않으시나요?
However, how do you see it?
그런데, 어떻게 보시나요?
All these pages?
이 페이지가 다요?
I am
그래요
most like the story plagiarism save to save Zhao.
대부분 이야기 표절은 Zhao를 구하기 위해 저장됩니다.
You mean Ying, the high noble of Wei country, right?
위나라의 대귀족 잉이라는 말이지?
Truly.
진심으로.
That person, Ying,
그 사람, 잉,
he used to be
그는 ~하곤했다
is a guardian
보호자입니다
same as me.
나와 같은.
But then
하지만
even became one of the four young masters of the warring country.
전국의 4대 청년이 되기도 했습니다.
From all corners of this country.
이 나라의 모든 곳에서.
Unexpected
예기치 않은
Qian Xiu also had the same ambition
Qian Xiu도 같은 야망을 갖고 있었습니다.
I have a nightmare
악몽을 꿨어요
I'm just blind.
나는 단지 장님입니다.
Good.
좋은.
Go ahead.
계속하세요.
Director Ding.
딩 감독.
I'll just go home alone.
그냥 집에 혼자 갈게요.
Can't.
캔트.
Master Shan Xia specifically ordered
Master Shan Xia가 특별히 주문한 것
must get you home safely
집에 안전하게 데려다줘야 해
Okay.
좋아요.
Didn't the lights just come on?
방금 불이 켜지지 않았나요?
Why is it dead now?
지금은 왜 죽었나요?